Well-kept silky hair.
柔顺的头发
A baby face that screams innocence.
天真的娃娃脸
Her innate airheaded personality.
她天生愚蠢的性格
It's true…
是真的…
According to my long experience in following idols,
根据我长期追偶像的经验
these types of girls gain popularity from hardcore otakus like crazy!
这种类型的女孩 在铁杆御宅族中人气非常高！
Your perspective and analysis are disturbing.
你的观点和分析令人不安
If she'll get popular, then great. Why don't you try scouting her?
如果她会受欢迎 那就太好了 你为什么不找她呢？
Well, you're right, but…
你说得对 但是
You know how Loli senpai and my destinies are entwined?
你知道我和萝莉学姐的命运 是如何交织对峙在一起的吗？
You do?
有吗？
I mean, doesn't she have like a bad attitude toward me?
我是说 她对我的态度不是很不好吗？
Isn't that because you keep saying "baking soda"?
那不是因为你一直提“小苏打”吗？
Anyhow, I'll message her to meet up, so at least try talking to her.
不管怎样 我会给她发信息 约她见面 所以至少试着跟她谈谈
If you still think you can't get along, then you can forget it.
如果你还觉得相处不来 那就算了
KANA ARIMA'S ACTING STANDS OUT FROM THE REST
（有马加奈演技脱颖而出）
THE STALKER WAS CREEPY BUT HE WAS SO GOOD-LOOKING
（跟踪狂很恐怖 但他长得很帅）
I NEED TO TALK TO YOU AFTER SCHOOL
（有事想和你谈谈 放学后有空吗）
What could it be?
会是什么事呢？
What does he need to talk to me so urgently about?
他这么急着要跟我谈什么？
Really?
真的吗？
Could it be about…
难道是关于…
How troublesome…
真麻烦啊
Really?
真的吗？
-Sorry for the wait. -Finally.
-抱歉 让你久等了 -终于来了
What took you so long?
你怎么现在才来？
Huh? You can wait there forever.
什么？你可以永远等下去
Why is your little sister here too?
你妹妹怎么也在这儿？
Because Ruby's the one who needs to talk to you.
因为就是露比要跟你谈谈
I regret bracing myself.
真后悔 我还做了准备
So, what is it? I'm busy unlike you, so keep it under 20 seconds.
所以是什么事？ 我很忙 不像你 20秒内说完
What a blatant attitude.
她还真是毫不避讳啊
Bro, if I asked her to become an idol now,
哥 如果我现在邀请她当偶像
that's like me saying that she's as cute as an idol!
就仿佛我认可她可爱到可以当偶像
That really gets on my nerves!
这真让我抓狂
What's this pride you have?
你这份自傲是哪来的？
Don't you want to start idol activities immediately?
你不想马上开始偶像活动吗？
Is this the time to be stubborn?
这是固执的时候吗？
You're right. It's true.
你说得对 是真的
Ms. Kana Arima.
有马加奈女士
Would you like to become an idol with me?
你愿意和我一起成为偶像吗？
Idol? Why all of a sudden?
偶像？怎么突然说这个？
There's a project to make a new idol unit at Ichigo Production.
莓制作公司有个项目 要制作一个新的偶像单元
And I'm looking for its members.
我在找成员
I heard you were a freelancer.
我听说你是个自由职业者
Well, to be frank, this would be a recruitment.
坦率地说 我们想招募你
Is this for real?
这是真的吗？
It's important and for real.
这很重要 而且是真的
Give me a little time to think about it.
给我点时间考虑一下
No, there's no way.
不 不可能
If I begin working as an idol, I'll lose the young actor type of jobs,
如果我开始当偶像 就没法再当演员
and my main work will become the rapidly changing idol-type jobs.
我的主要工作将变为 瞬息万变的偶像型工作
If I don't become a hit idol, I lose both jobs.
如果我不能成为当红偶像 就会丢掉两份工作
The risk is too high freelance-wise.
对于自由职业者来说 风险太高了
However…
然而…
Ruby Hoshino.
星野露比
I don't know why,
我不知道为什么
but this girl bears some kind of resemblance to the genius idol Ai.
但这个女孩有几分像天才偶像爱
I've only worked with Ai once,
我只跟爱合作过一次
but she was meant to become a real star.
但她注定要成为真正的明星
My senses as an entertainer sees potential in this girl.
作为艺人 我看到了这个女孩的潜力
But Ichigo Production isn't a major agency and has no record of any new projects.
但莓制作公司不是一家大型经纪公司 也没有任何新项目的记录
First of all, I'm not cute enough to become popular as an idol.
最重要的是我不够可爱 不能成为受欢迎的偶像
I'm not that foolish to take a wild gamble.
我还不至于傻到去冒险
-I'm sorry, but-- -Please.
-对不起 但是… -拜托
Kana Arima.
有马加奈
Please become an idol with my sister.
拜托跟我妹妹一起当偶像吧
But I'm not that cute--
但我没那么可爱
No, you are cute.
不 你很可爱
I wouldn't ask you to become an idol so lightly.
我不会贸然要求你当偶像
Arima, you're much cuter than many of those idols out there.
有马 你比外面的那些偶像可爱多了
If it's you, I can put my precious sister under your care.
如果是你 我可以把宝贝妹妹交给你照顾
Uh, but…
但是…
Please, become an idol.
拜托 成为偶像吧
-I… I can't! -Please.
-我做不到 -求你了
I'm not doing it!
我不当！
Arima, I'm asking you because I trust you.
有马 我问你是因为我信任你
Jeez! No matter how many times you ask, no means no!
天啊 不管你问多少次 不行就是不行！
I won't ever do it!
我永远不会当偶像！
KANA ARIMA
（有马加奈）
Welcome to Ichigo Production. We're happy to have you onboard.
欢迎来到莓制作公司 很高兴你能加入我们
My brain knows I shouldn't! So how do I always end up like this?!
我的大脑知道不应该这样 那我最后怎么总是这样呢？
Let's work together, Senpai!
我们一起努力吧 学姐
I didn't think you'd really bring her over.
我没想到你真带她过来了
What kind of method did you use?
你用的是什么方法？
Nothing special. Just a personality reading.
没什么特别的 对她的个性解读而已
Kana Arima is very sympathetic and weak under pressure.
有马加奈非常有同情心 抗压能力差
According to her personality, I thought a sob story or over-pressuring would work,
根据她的性格 我觉得 一个悲伤的故事或者过度施压会有用
and sure enough, it did.
果然如此
You know…
你呀
If you keep doing that kind of stuff, you're gonna get punished someday.
如果你继续这样做 总有一天你会受到惩罚的
Be careful when you walk at night.
走夜路小心点
I don't think I've done anything bad.
我不认为我做了什么坏事
You making fun of me?!
你在取笑我？
It's not like I lied about anything.
我又没撒谎
Well…
那个…
my meaningless title as an ex-genius child actress has only changed
我毫无意义的前天才童星头衔
to an ex-genius child actress idol, that's all.
只是变成了前天才童星偶像 仅此而已
Either way, I did need a boost one way or another.
不管怎样 我确实需要这样或那样的鼓励
You're so desperate to convince yourself of reality.
你太急于说服自己相信现实了
Besides,
而且
if I join the same agency as him, we'll be able to work together more.
如果我加入他的经纪公司 合作就会更多了
There could be some kind of skill I can learn from him.
也许我能从他身上学到一些技巧
Really?
真的吗？
Hey, doesn't Aqua have any upcoming jobs or anything?
难道阿夸没接到新的工作吗？
Umm, well, he does.
有是有…
That's a bitter look…
你的表情很痛苦
This.
这个
What?
什么？
Aqua's dating?!
阿夸要去恋爱节目？
WE'RE ABOUT TO FALL IN LOVE ♥ FOR REAL
（《现在开始认真恋爱》）
A NEW SEASON KICKS OFF
（新一季开始了）
THE START OF A FRESH SEASON OF LOVE
（新一季《现恋》开播）
THE SIX PARTICIPATING MEMBERS THIS TIME ARE…
（这次参加的六名成员是…）
Hello!
你好
Um, I'm Yuki Sumi. I'm a 1st year in high school.
我是鹫见夕雪 在读高中一年级
She has a nice style!
她很会穿衣服
She looks good from head to toe.
她从头到脚都很好看
I'm Nobuyuki Kumano. I'm good at dancing.
我是熊野信行 我擅长跳舞
NOBUYUKI KUMANO DANCER - 2ND YEAR
（熊野信行 舞者 高中二年级）
I'm Akane Kurokawa, a 2nd year in high school. I'm an actress.
我是黑川茜 高中二年级 我是一名演员
Ugh, there she is.
她来了
Oh, you know her?
你认识她？
Well, yeah…
算是吧
I'm Mem-cho, a 3rd year in high school. I stream on YouTube!
我是MEM啾 高中三年级 我在油管上直播
Nice to meet you!
很高兴认识你们
So these types appear too, huh.
所以这个类型也出现了
She's so cute!
她太可爱了
I'm Kengo Morimoto. I'm in a band. Nice meeting everyone.
我是森本剑吾 乐队成员 很高兴认识大家
KENGO MORIMOTO MUSICIAN - 3RD YEAR
（森本剑吾 音乐家 高中三年级）
Oh, what year are you?
你们几年级？
Second year.
二年级
Third year.
三年级
I see.
这样啊
So high schoolers who work in showbiz
所以是在娱乐圈工作的高中生们
deepen their relationships through various events on weekends.
通过周末的各种活动加深他们的关系
And you get to see who gets together or not at the end of the show.
在节目最后 你可以看到他们有没有在一起
Since this is Producer Kaburagi's program, everybody has a pretty face.
因为这是镝木制片人的节目 所以大家长得都很好看
Oh, it's Bro.
是哥哥
I'm Aqua. I'm getting super nervous. Everyone, nice to meet you!
我是阿夸 我超级紧张 大家好 很高兴认识你们
Who the hell is that?!
那到底是谁？
Bro's usually the dark type who emits a negative aura!
我哥通常是那种 散发着负面光环的黑暗类型
He's totally a poser!
他真是个装腔作势的人
Wow, so cool!
太酷了
I admire actors!
我很崇拜演员
Agh, my brother's hard on these types of girls who act cutesy.
我哥对这种装腔作势的女孩很严厉
So this girl's out.
所以这个女孩出局了
Mem-cho, you're cute too. You're making me really blush.
MEM啾 你也很可爱 你真让我脸红
Huh? Drop dead.
什么？去死吧
What's with him?!
他怎么了？
He told me that I was cute only when I was being recruited!
他只有在我被招募的时候 才说我很可爱
He's getting carried away being surrounded by women.
他被女人包围得有点忘乎所以了
I'll have to lecture him later.
我待会儿要教训他一顿
So my brother's just a wolf after all.
所以我哥终究不过是个男的
This is what happens as soon as men find some easy prey.
一旦男人找到了容易捕获的猎物 就会发生这种情况
Calm down, you two. This is all for show.
冷静点 你们俩 这都是为了做节目
If he doesn't act that way, the show wouldn't hold up, right?
如果他不这么做 节目就进行不下去了 对吧？
Though I understand seeing a familiar guy flirting with other women is irritating.
虽然我能理解看到一个熟悉的男人 和其他女人调情很让人恼火
Aqua is an actor too.
阿夸也是一名演员
I'm sure he's probably there knowing that he has to act out a guy like that.
我敢肯定 他知道得演个那样的男人
Acting…
是演技啊
I know that, but…
我知道 但是
Don't they actually ask each other out and become couples at the end?
他们不是真的会约对方出去 最后成为情侣吗？
That's right.
没错
Even if it's an act, they'll have to go through with it.
即使是演戏 他们也得演到底
If they do become a couple, don't they kiss and stuff?
如果他们真的成了情侣 不是要接吻什么的吗？
That's how it usually goes.
通常是这样
Why did he accept a show like this?
他为什么要接受这样的节目？
If you're going to continue as an actress too,
如果你还想继续当演员
scenes with kissing and the sort will eventually be demanded.
最终也会被要求拍吻戏之类的
You have to accept that as part of the job.
你必须接受这是工作的一部分
If you keep prudish views in this field, it's going to weigh you down later.
如果你继续在这个领域保守 以后会拖累你的
I know that, but…
我知道 但是…
-So, this is my dog! -Uh-huh.
-对了 这是我的狗 -嗯
See? Cute, huh? Look!
看 可爱吧 看啊
Uh-huh, so cute.
太可爱了
What a drag.
烦死了
It's tough having these empty conversations where all I can do is agree…
很难进行这些空洞的对话 我能做的就是赞同
Why do I have to put up with this?
我为什么要忍受这些？
If you go on this show for me,
如果你上我这个节目
I'll tell you a deep inside story that Ai's agency doesn't even know.
我会告诉你一个 连爱的经纪公司都不知道的内幕
That itself could be about Ai's relationships with men.
可能跟爱与男性的情感关系有关
I'll just have to go through with it.
我只能这么做了
So I can get information about Ai from Producer Kaburagi.
这样我就能从镝木制片人那里 得到关于爱的信息
That should become a clue to finding our father.
这应该是找到我们父亲的线索
This is how the show flows…
这就是节目的流程
Uh, we don't mind if everyone talks freely with each other.
我们不介意大家自由交谈
However, just be careful of the static camera angles please.
但是请注意静态相机的角度
When the cameraman closes up, if it's possible,
当摄影师关闭镜头时 如果可能的话
it would help us if you could recap the conversation you were just having.
复述一下刚才的对话 对我们会有帮助
Okay!
好了
The history of reality dating shows have reached 20 years,
恋爱类真人秀节目 已经有20年的历史了
so its know-how has been built up to some degree.
所以它的专业知识也有了一定的积累
While guaranteeing its entertainment side of the program,
在保证节目娱乐性的同时
there are ways to stage reality based on the individuals' personalities.
也有办法根据每个人的个性 来呈现现实
Um, am I doing this okay?
我这样做对吗？
Uh, I think that's fine at first.
我觉得一开始没问题
Next time, if you can close the distance a bit and chat, that would help.
下次如果你们能拉近一点距离 聊聊天 那会有帮助的
Since the audience wants excitement too.
因为观众也想要刺激
I see…
明白了
So these shows really don't have a script.
所以这些节目真的没有剧本
I don't know what to talk about at all.
我根本不知道该说什么
I know!
我懂
Reality shows don't have a script.
真人秀没有剧本
But the staging exists.
但是有设定的
It's up to us to take the director's words as advice or directions.
由我们自己决定 是否把导演的话当作建议或指示
I'm a scaredy cat and not aggressive. Nor am I good at talking.
我胆子很小 没有攻击性 我也不擅长说话
So I bet I'm just gonna fade out.
所以我慢慢就会消失了
Why did you take on this job?
你为什么接受这份工作？
Our agency's star is the type to never decline jobs.
我们经纪公司的主推明星 是那种从不拒绝工作的人
That person takes all the jobs that come in, so I'm bored all year round.
那个人接手了所有的工作 所以我一年到头都很无聊
So I kind of wanted to fight my way out.
我想要冲出重围
That's when Mr. Kaburagi…
就在这时 镝木先生…
Ah.
这样啊
It was perfect since I never dated much until now anyway.
这个机会很好 因为直到现在 我从来没谈过恋爱
Liar.
骗人的吧
Hey, it's not a lie.
我没骗人
I'm still a 1st year in high school.
我还在上高一
If you think we're all dating just because we're an entertainer, you're wrong.
如果你认为我们是艺人 就会谈恋爱 那你就错了
Don't you have any interest in dating?
你对恋爱不感兴趣吗？
Of course I do. I am a guy after all.
我当然感兴趣 我毕竟是个男人
But, I can't get over an old crush…
但我忘不了从前的恋情
No, come to think of it, I don't even know if that was a crush.
不对 仔细想想 我都不知道那算不算恋爱
I haven't fully gotten over it yet, so I can't really say…
我还没有完全走出来 所以真的不好说…
Hm? It's complicated?
什么？很复杂？
Oh, like you had a crush on your teacher?
就像你喜欢上你的老师一样？
That's pretty close.
非常接近
Then you'll need to overcome that.
那你就需要克服它
Did you know?
你知道吗？
Last season's couple kissed at the end!
上一季的情侣最后接吻了
Yeah. I did do my research.
是的 我也做了些调查
I was worried if there would be any good guys…
我还担心会不会有好男人
but I may be able to kiss if it's you.
但如果是你 我也许可以吻你
Wha…
什…
Behind me.
看我身后
The cameraman's filming.
摄影师正在拍摄
Don't look toward the camera.
不要看向摄影机
This part will surely be used.
这部分肯定会用到
Let's get along.
我们好好相处吧
She's got a sly personality. And she said she's a scaredy cat?
她真狡猾 还说自己胆小？
I see, so this is a reality show.
我明白了 这就是真人秀
I am your sister supposedly,
我是你妹妹
so I don't want my brother dating a type of person that I don't like.
我不想让我哥跟我不喜欢的人约会
Which is why I am going to choose who you should date.
所以我来决定你跟谁约会
How selfish can you be?
真是自作主张啊
My recommendation is… Yuki-pon!
我的建议是夕雪
I'm sure this girl is a good innocent girl!
我相信她是个天真的好女孩
You're a poor judge of character, so don't date for a while.
你不会看人 所以暂时别谈恋爱
Huh?!
什么？
Frill is absent again today.
芙莉露今天又休息吗
She did say a shoot for a new drama started,
她说新剧开始拍摄了
so maybe she's busy?
所以她可能很忙吧？
Hm.
是吗
What about you, Minami?
你呢 奈美？
I'm going to my shoot after school.
我放学后要去拍摄
I see…
这样啊
My brother's at his shoot today too.
我哥今天也去拍摄了
Senpai, you're used to not having work, right?
学姐 你已经习惯不用工作了吧？
What do you usually do?
你通常做什么？
Do you want me to throw a jab at your chin and shake your brain?
你想让我朝你下巴打一拳 然后晃你脑袋吗？
If you're bored, you should study.
如果你觉得无聊 应该去学习
Idols are short-term jobs you can barely survive off of even if you do get popular.
当偶像是短期工作 即使 你真的很受欢迎 也很难靠它生存
Doing something to get into a good college will benefit your life more.
为进入一所好大学而努力 对你的生活更有好处
That's brutally frank of you…
你真是太坦率了
Isn't there something I could do right now?
我现在不能做些什么吗？
The work of new idols are
新偶像们的工作就是
just singing and dancing at concert halls.
在小剧场里唱歌、跳舞
And sometimes accepting jobs from the media, right?
有时还会接受媒体给的工作 对吧？
We don't have any songs or even a group name yet.
我们还没有歌曲 甚至连团名都没有
What's there for us to do right now?
我们现在要做什么？
We don't have a group name yet, because you're the one griping about it!
我们还没有团名 因为你在抱怨！
Because it'll become real if we come up with a name.
因为如果我们想出了团名 就真要当偶像了
I haven't really made up my mind yet to call myself an idol.
我还没有真正下定决心称自己为偶像
Why not? Idol Kana Arima.
有什么不好？偶像有马加奈
How embarrassing!
好羞耻啊
A self-proclaimed idol without any achievements…
一个没有任何成就的自封偶像
How do I explain that to my parents?!
我该怎么跟我父母解释？
So if you have achieved something, would you make up your mind?
所以如果你已经取得了一些成就 就会下定决心吗？
Then let's achieve something.
那我们就成就点什么吧
What is this cheap camera?
这廉价的相机是怎么回事？
Even if it's cheap, it's enough.
即使很便宜 功能也足够了
It was the norm for new idols
不久前
to pass out flyers or perform joint concerts until a while ago.
新偶像发传单 或举行联合演唱会还是常态
But times have changed.
但时代变了
The center of idol culture is now on the internet.
偶像文化的中心现在是在互联网上
This is the most cost-efficient place to take root.
这是最具成本效益的生根之地
Let's begin with spreading your names on the internet.
我们先从在互联网上蹿红开始吧
You mean to become YouTubers?
你的意思是成为油管博主？
Yup. If we make regular customers and call them to concerts, isn't that efficient?
对 先在网上积累关注者 再号召他们去听现场 很有效率吧？
Mrs. Miyako's so smart!
京子社长好聪明啊
CEO… aren't you underestimating the internet?
社长 你是不是低估了互联网？
Even if you upload this girl with nothing but a good face,
即使你上传这个花瓶女孩的视频
we'll only hit a few thousand subscribers at most.
我们最多也只能吸引几千名订阅者
Say what?
你说什么？
I don't know if we'll hit 10,000 even with my fans.
即使加上我的粉丝 我也不知道能不能达到一万
Since probably only 1% of that will participate in a real event,
线下活动能动员参加的人数只有 线上粉丝的1%
I think it'll be pretty tough.
我认为这将是相当困难的
That's if an amateur tried doing that.
这是业余爱好者尝试的结果
But Ichigo Production's strength lies within the internet,
但莓制作公司在互联网上很有优势
we possess many streamers.
我们有很多主播
We have the know-how.
有专业人士支持
I just grabbed someone who can help you, so go learn a lot from him.
我刚找到一个能帮你们的人 多去跟他学学
Okay, I'll leave the rest to you!
好了 剩下就交给你了
Leave it to me!
交给我吧
It's…
这是…
a freak!
变态啊！
Oh, it's Pieyon!
是啾啾仔
What? Who?!
什么？谁？
He's super popular among young kids!
他在小孩子中非常受欢迎
You don't know the masked fitness YouTuber, Pieyon?!
你不认识蒙面健身 油管博主 啾啾仔吗？
He's our top seller!
他是我们最能赚钱的艺人
First of all, the "masked fitness" genre is new to me!
首先 “蒙面健身”这一类型 对我来说是全新的
I don't watch YouTube that much.
我不太看油管
So this is what strikes kids' interests nowadays.
这就是现在的孩子们感兴趣的东西
We sure live in a distorted society.
我们生活在一个扭曲的社会里
How dare you talk like that to Pieyon…
你竟敢这样跟啾啾仔说话
Mr. Pieyon, tell her off!
啾啾仔先生 反驳她
The internet is just about making strong impressions after all.
毕竟 互联网只是为了 给人留下深刻的印象
It's like a mascot business reusing television schemes…
这就像重复利用着电视企划的 吉祥物产业
I make 100 million a year.
我年收入一个亿哦
I apologize for my foolish words.
我为我的愚蠢言论道歉
Listen well. There are several techniques in order to gain subscribers.
听好 有几种技巧可以获得订阅者
What do you think they are?
你们认为是什么？
Daily uploads!
每天上传
Original popularity?
原本的知名度？
Uh-huh, right!
对了
But you two don't have the guts to upload daily or have original popularity, do you?
但你们俩既不能做到每天上传 也没有原本知名度加持 对吧？
Brutal.
真残酷啊
However, there's a shortcut to gaining subscribers easily!
然而 有一个捷径 可以轻松获得订阅者
We've been waiting, Sensei!
我们洗耳恭听 老师
Please tell us!
请告诉我们
That is…
那就是…
Peep, peep! The Pieyon Channel!
啾啾！啾啾仔频道
So today, we have a collaboration!
今天 有人跟我一起合作
COLLABORATION
（合作）
I guess there's an idol unit at our agency now?
我们公司大概组了个偶像团体
They're gonna start one, so they told me to use them on my channel.
要开一个新频道 公司让我在自己频道多用用新人
I thought of refusing at first!
起初我想过拒绝
But since the CEO insisted…
但既然社长坚持…
So let's begin our plan today!
不管怎么说 让我们开始今天的企划吧！
Aim for macho muscles!
目标是有男子气概的肌肉
Even if you peep, don't give up and fight!
即使你累了 也不要放弃战斗
Now flutter, muscles!
现在动起来 肌肉们
Break out of your shell, muscles!
破壳而出 肌肉们
Pieyon Dance Bootcamp!
啾啾仔舞蹈训练营
If they keep up with me for one hour, they can show their faces!
如果她们能跟上我一个小时 我就让她们露脸！
Everybody starts with chick muscles!
每个人都从一点肌肉开始
Be born, new muscles!
出生吧 新肌肉
Before you start chirping, do it!
在你开始唧唧喳喳之前 先动起来吧
You can wear a mask today too! Peep, peep!
你今天也可以蒙面
This world is survival of the fittest So do it!
这个世界是适者生存的 所以去做吧
Power is strength! Let's survive this tough industry!
权力就是力量 让我们在这个艰难的行业中生存下来
Sit down, stretch out your legs And lift your heels.
坐下 伸展双腿 抬起脚后跟
Keep this position…
保持这个姿势
This is tough!
好难啊
Since he claims to be a fitness YouTuber, he sure makes it tough!
既然他声称自己是健身博主 动作肯定很难
He wants us to dance with this stupid mask on? Is he trying to kill us?!
他想让我们戴着这个 愚蠢的面具跳舞？他想杀了我们吗？
The pose of the silent cicada!
沉默的蝉的姿势
I need oxygen!
我需要氧气！
The pose of the insomniac bear!
失眠熊的姿势
Please think about oxygen!
请考虑给氧气瓶！
Why did it turn out this way?
为什么事情会变成这样？
The best way to advertise is a collaboration after all.
毕竟 最好的推广方式是合作
To collaborate with a famous YouTuber is the quickest way!
与著名的博主合作是最快的方法
You'll appear on my channel this time, but what should we do?
这次你们会出现在我的频道上 但我们该怎么做？
You two are idols after all, so should we do like a wake-up prank?
你们俩毕竟是偶像 我们是不是该搞个叫醒恶作剧？
Ah, that sounds good.
听起来不错
Huh? But…
什么？但是
If we're told about it beforehand, it wouldn't be a prank, right?
如果事先告诉我们了 那就不是恶作剧了 对吧？
Are you seriously saying that?
你这么说是认真的吗？
What if the crew went to film an idol waking up and she was sleeping with a guy?
如果剧组去拍一个偶像醒来时 发现她在和一个男人睡觉怎么办？
Those shows usually notify the person the day before.
这些节目 通常会在前一天通知要拍的人
Really?!
真的吗？
But this is our very first job.
但这是我们第一份工作
I don't want to lie.
我不想撒谎
So it comes down to this?! This is the extreme opposite!
结果就是这样？这是完全相反的
I can tolerate this because I go jogging,
我可以忍 因为我经常慢跑
but for a complete amateur like her…
但对于像她这样的业余人士来说…
This is tough! It's so tough I'm gonna die!
这太难了 我要死了
The hatching pose!
孵化的姿势
Well done! You may take off your masks now and introduce yourselves!
做得好 你们现在可以摘下面具 做自我介绍了
I belong to Ichigo Production, I'm Ruby Hoshino.
我是莓制作公司的星野露比
I'm a self-proclaimed idol!
我自称是一位偶像
And you!
还有你
I'm Kana Arima, a self-proclaimed idol! Hello!
我是有马加奈 自称偶像 你们好
Yes, yes, I've heard of the name.
是的 我听说过这个名字
Only "heard of"?
只是“听说过”？
But well done.
你们表现很好
I was going to edit it to make it look like it was an hour,
我本来想剪辑一下 让它看起来像一个小时
but you two actually did it.
但你们俩真的做到了
It's not something the audience will see.
现在这些并不是观众会看到的东西
But the people on set are always watching,
但片场的人一直在看
so I like you two.
所以我喜欢你们俩
Oh, I forgot to ask something important!
我忘了问一件重要的事情
Do you two have a group name?
你们俩有团名吗？
Uh…
那个…
Just choose whatever you want, Ruby.
随便你选吧 露比
You sure?
可以吗？
Um, then our group name is…
那我们的团名是
B Komachi!
B小町
What? Is that okay to use?
什么？用这个没问题吗？
AFTER MAKING THE B KOMACHI IDOLS DANCE FOR ONE HOUR…!!
（在让B小町偶像们 跳了一个小时的舞后…）
Subtitle translation by: Kanami Kitabayashi
字幕翻译：宋宛娇